[
    {
        "front": "～くん",
        "back": "(suffix for calling one's male friend or jr.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "じだい",
        "back": "period",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんか（する）",
        "back": "fight / to fight",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいせき",
        "back": "marks",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "まじめな",
        "back": "serious",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "うんどう（する）",
        "back": "exercise / to exercise",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "とくいな",
        "back": "be good at",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいかい",
        "back": "contest",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうしょう（する）",
        "back": "to win",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほめる",
        "back": "to praise",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひさしぶり",
        "back": "a long time",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "なくなる",
        "back": "to disappear (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）なくす",
        "back": "to lose (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    },
    {
        "front": "さびしい",
        "back": "sad; lonely",
        "chapter": "N4 C20"
    }
]